Hi Sherise.Hello Sherise.
嗨 Sherise. 哈喽 Sherise.
Where's Sherise?
Sherise在哪里?
Has Sherise gone to the movies?
Sherise去看电影了吗?
No,she hasn't.
不, 她没有.
She's right here! Wuh wuh wuh...
她就在这里! wuh wuh wuh...
Excuse me?
打搅一下?
Oh! Good morning.
Oh, 早安.
Good morning,Wendy. Friend of yours?
早安, Wendy. 你朋友?
That's Sherise.
那是Sherise.
Where's Sherise?
Sherise在哪里?
Sherise is in the restaurant.
Sherise在餐厅里
The question is,who is Sherise?
问题是, Sherise是谁?
Nina's baby.
Nina的宝宝
Oh.And where is Nina?
Oh.那么Nina在哪里?
She's at a meeting.
她在开会.
And where's the meeting?
会议在哪里?
At the Children's Center.
在儿童中心.
Nina's gone to a meeting at the Children's Center,
Nina(已经)去开会了 在儿童中心,
and her baby is here?
她的宝宝在这里?
That's right.
对的
Has Sherise gone to the meeting?
Sherise去开会了吗?
No,she hasn't.
不, 她没有
Why isn't Sherise at the Children's Center?
为什么Sherise没有在儿童中心?
Or at home,at Sherise's house?
或在家, 在Sherise的房子里?
Nina's baby sitter is sick,OK?
Nina的保姆生病了,ok?
Oh,so the baby sitter's gone home.
Oh,so 保姆(已经)回家去了.
But not Sherise!Sherise is at work.
但Sherise没有! Sherise在工作.
Excuse me?
打搅一下?
Yes.Can I help...? Can I help you?
是.我可以帮...? 我可以帮你吗?
Do you know where the Children's center is?
你知道儿童中心在哪吗?
Why,yes.